http://www.ross-tech.com/privacy.php

Shop  Info
F.A.Q.
Forum
Ross-Tech's Privacy Policy:
1. General:  It is our policy to keep all
personal information about our customers strictly confidential.
We will not give our customers' personal information to anyone
else, except as follows:
1.1 If/when required by law:  We are subject to the
laws of the United States and the Commonwealth of
Pennsylvania.  Thus if a US or Pennsylvania law or court
order requires us
to divulge customer data, we have little choice in the matter.
1.2 Payment fraud:  We will cooperate fully with
any investigation of payment fraud where said fraud has been
committed against us or any of our distributors or resellers.
1.3 Theft:  We will cooperate fully with
any investigation of theft, where a registered user, distributor, or reseller
has reported one or more products stolen.
1.4 Distributor network:  We may share a customer's
contact information with the distributor or reseller who
originally purchased that customer's particular system from us, or who
requests an upgrade or support on that customer's behalf.
2. Personal Information:  Personal information means information
that can identify you as an individual. We collect information about you and
your use of our products remotely and pursuant to your
purchase, registration, and support requests.
Personal Information does not include general, statistical, aggregated or
anonymized information.
2.1 Your Consent:  By providing your personal
information to us when purchasing a product directly from us,
registering one of our products that your purchased elsewhere,  requesting
support for one of our products, or using one of our products,  you consent to us collecting and
storing that information and using it accordance with the
other clauses of this policy.
2.2 Security Measures:  We will take, implement and maintain all such technical and
organizational security procedures and measures as may be necessary or appropriate to preserve the security and confidentiality of any personal information
in our possession, and will apply industry acceptable means to protect such information against
unauthorized or unlawful disclosure or access.
3. How and why we collect information about you:
We may collect personal information under the following
circumstances and for the purposes stated:.
3.1 When you order a product from us:  In that case,
we collect personal information from you necessary to fulfill your order
and to provide future support for the product(s) you purchase.
3.2 When you register a product with us:  In that case,
we collect personal information from you to establish
your eligibility for support and future product updates/upgrades.
3.2 When you contact us for support:  In that
case, we collect personal information from you as necessary
to establish your eligibility and to provide you with the assistance you seek.
3.4 When you use our software:  In that case, we
may collect information allowing us improve our products,
protect them from theft,
and provide better support.
4. Length of Storage:
Our policy is to store personal data only for as long as is
necessary for the purposes set out in section 3 above.
This may vary depending on the type of data and the
specific applicable purpose(s).
5. Ownership:
You acknowledge and agree that we retain ownership of all data
stored on our systems.
6. Your Rights:
We acknowledge that residents of the European Union have certain rights under the
General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation Regulation 2016/679),
among them:
6.1 The right to access the personal data that we hold about you:
You may request a copy of the personal data we hold about
you.
6.2 The right to request corrections:  If we hold
any personal data about you that is incorrect or incomplete, you may request that
we correct that data.
6.3 The right to be forgotten:  You may request
that we delete any personal data we hold about you..
6.4 Exercising these rights:  In order to exercise these rights
(or others that the GDPR may confer upon you) please contact us us.  Understand
that we may need to take additional steps to confirm your
identity before we can comply with such requests.
otherwise noted, all content on this site is Copyright (c) 2000-2017 by
Ross-Tech LLC.  All rights reserved."VCDS", "VCDS-Mobile" and
"HEX-NET" are Registered Trademarks of Ross-Tech, LLC.
Ross-Tech is not affiliated with the Volkswagen Group in any way.
